# Mohammadhosein Shakiba

#### researcher at int-n.info

Mashhad

shakiba@int-n.info

I'm a third-year undergrad, majoring in cell and molecular biology. I'm passionate about neuroscience and spend my free time doing research synthesis and meta-analysis. I'm also honing my skills in computer science, and statistics for scientific and analytical projects.

# Work Experience

#### Researcher

int-n.info

2023 to Present

- Conduct research synthesis and meta-analysis
- Lead and collaborate with a team of fellow researchers

### **English Teacher**

Safir Language Academy - Tehrān 2022 to 2023

- Taught English to 100+ individuals of all ages using the ESA method
- Developed course materials, schedules, and quizzes
- Completed a Teacher Training course and earned a certificate

### **Student Intern**

Molecular lab., Institut Pasteur - Tehrān 2022 to 2022

- Completed a 120-hour on-site program and earned a certificate
- Formulated custom buffers for extraction protocols
- Activities included DNA extraction, RNA extraction, and PCR procedures
- Gained hands-on experience in key laboratory techniques

# Education

# **Bachelor of Science in Cell Biology**

Ferdowsi University of Mashhad - Mashhad 2021 to Present

#### **High School Diploma**

National Organization for Development of Exceptional Talents (Sampad) - Tehrān 2018 to 2021

#### Skills

- Python
- R
- Git
- Math
- Statistics
- SOL
- · Machine learning

# Languages

- Persian Fluent
- English Fluent

#### Certifications and Licenses

# **CS50x (Harvard University)**

Introduction to the intellectual enterprises of computer science and the art of programming. https://cs50.harvard.edu/certificates/2fec4b3b-b324-4c23-9b5c-7632bbd40fbe

# **CS50P** (Harvard University)

Introduction to Programming with Python.

https://cs50.harvard.edu/certificates/30c89e28-bb58-46a6-a4d1-ac180ff48c29

### **Cancer Biology (Johns Hopkins University)**

Introduction to the molecular biology of cancer (oncogenes and tumor suppressor genes) as well as the biologic hallmarks of cancer.

https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/specialization/certificate/DM3KFBDJXRJT

# Data Analysis with R (Duke University)

Statistical mastery of data analysis including basic data visualization, statistical testing and inference, and linear modeling.

https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/specialization/certificate/BY4U3Y95N9PZ

#### **Data Science (Sharif University of Technology)**

MicroMasters Program

- Python Programming
- Mathematics for AI & Data Science
- Programming for Data Analysis
- Principles and Techniques in Data Science
- Big Data Processing and Analysis
- Machine Learning

# **Publications**

#### **ORCID**

https://orcid.org/0009-0003-4404-7759

### **GitHub**

https://github.com/abikahs

# Additional Information

#### Other Certifications:

Introduction to Genetics and Evolution (Duke University) https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/EK75PXFAQ6S7

Introduction to Psychology (Yale University) https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/336GDCV52Q53

Introduction to Neurobiology (The University of Chicago) https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/SPXWHULGWVWD